{
    "subject": "resource/Heliotropium_curassavicum",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Heliotropium_curassavicum",
    "human_readable": "Heliotropium curassavicum is primarily about Heliotropium curassavicum.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9831079840660095,
            "question": "What is Heliotropium curassavicum primarily about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.962764322757721,
            "question": "Is there a common name for Heliotropium curassavicum?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9233459234237671,
            "question": "What are the characteristics of Heliotropium curassavicum?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8773056268692017,
            "question": "What is the scientific classification of Heliotropium curassavicum?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.875616729259491,
            "question": "Is there any cultural significance associated with Heliotropium curassavicum?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8340091109275818,
            "question": "What are the ecological benefits of Heliotropium curassavicum?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8185358047485352,
            "question": "Where does Heliotropium curassavicum typically grow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7534977793693542,
            "question": "How does Heliotropium curassavicum reproduce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6947872042655945,
            "question": "Does Heliotropium curassavicum have any medicinal uses?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6497008204460144,
            "question": "Are there any threats to the survival of Heliotropium curassavicum?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Heliotropium curassavicum is primarily about Heliotropium curassavicum.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4283_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Heliotropium curassavicum have any medicinal uses?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4283_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does Heliotropium curassavicum reproduce?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4283_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does Heliotropium curassavicum typically grow?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4283_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4283_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4283_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4283_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4283_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4283_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4283_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4283_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4283_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4283_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4283_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents provide detailed information about Heliotropium curassavicum, its characteristics, growing conditions, and synonyms, indicating that it is primarily about Heliotropium curassavicum."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide various descriptions and characteristics related to Heliotropium curassavicum, confirming that the information is indeed primarily about this plant species."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}